ZHANDOS SAPARBAYEV

Inter Back End Developer, Junior Java Developer

I am a modest guy who wants to become a backend developer in the IT field with all his might. I can work in a team and know how to use github. I have a simple goal, it is to develop myself by practicing with the best specialists and gaining experience.

EXPERIENCE

Almaty, Kazakhstan 2020 - May 2022

Java Developer

SDU

University courses: Introduction to Java, Java 2, Introduction to Algorithms, Advanced Algorithms.

Almaty, Kazakhstan Sep 2021 - May 2022

Backend Developer

SDU

University courses: Web programming: back end, Web programming: front end.

EDUCATION

Saryagash, Kazakhstan Sep 2012 - May 2020

Almaty, Kaskelen, Kazakhstan Sep 2020 - Present

High school

№10 named of K.Satbayev

Bachelor

Suleyman Demirel University

I am a second year student.

PROJECTS

My projects in github: https://github.com/zhandos200103201?tab=repositories

CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES

https://www.sololearn.com/certificates/course/en/24885456/1068/landscape/png

CONTACT INFORMATION

Email

saparbayevzh03@gmail.com

Address

Abylai khan 1/1, 040900 Kas kelen, Kazakhstan

Phone

8-(778)-883-9586

Date of birth

Feb 5, 2003

Nationality

kazakh

Link

Zhandos Saparbayev

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Problem-Solving
- Hardcoding
- Java
- Python
- SQLite
- Base Php

LANGUAGES

English

Intermediate

Russian

Advanced

Kazakh

Native